<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Juha Liikala | Front-End Engineer | Oulu, Finland</title>
    <link>https://www.itsmejuha.co/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Juha Liikala | Front-End Engineer | Oulu, Finland</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 11:10:51 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.itsmejuha.co/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s Brewing?</title>
      <link>https://www.itsmejuha.co/whats-brewing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 11:10:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsmejuha.co/whats-brewing/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s brewing?&amp;rdquo; section of this site. This is where I list some of the stuff I&amp;rsquo;ve been recently involved with and also something that I&amp;rsquo;m going to be working on next.
What I&amp;rsquo;m Up To Right Now&amp;hellip;  Current Work: Working full-time in front-end development / product design role at Synopsys, building web based tools that help make software safer Writing &amp;amp; Reading: In 2018, I decided to start writing again regularly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing</title>
      <link>https://www.itsmejuha.co/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 13:10:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsmejuha.co/writing/</guid>
      <description>Writing is something I&amp;rsquo;ve always enjoyed doing, but seldom have in a regular manner. In December 2017, I decided to start building up the habit again by writing something new every week on Medium.com.
I haven&amp;rsquo;t set up a blog here on my personal website yet, but I&amp;rsquo;m considering it if I manage to keep up with my writing properly in 2018 :)
These are my latest on Medium.com:  So Interneters, where do you hang out these days (a brief history in blogging)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading</title>
      <link>https://www.itsmejuha.co/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 19:12:42 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsmejuha.co/reading/</guid>
      <description>I usually read 15-30 minutes each day just before bedtime. I&amp;rsquo;ve found it to be a great way for minimizing screen time in the evening (which I get plenty enough during the daytime already).
Latest from the book reading list:  The Power Of Habit by Charles Duhigg - Amazon.co.uk Machine, Platform, Crowd by Andrew McAfee and Erik Brynjolfsson - Amazon.co.uk The Fourth Industrial Revolution by Klaus Schwab - Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archives</title>
      <link>https://www.itsmejuha.co/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 16:13:08 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsmejuha.co/archives/</guid>
      <description>Old stuff. Archive of guest appearances on other blogs, Q&amp;amp;A listicles and more. Proceed with caution 😀. For the latest in writing, go here.
2015  Dive into the life of a traveler and digital nomad - About.me blog 8 reasons we hired a virtual assistant - Huffington Post 15 tips for managing remote workers - SmartBrief  2014  12 outdated web features that need to disappear in 2014 - Mashable 9 marketing mistakes that make you look like a rookie - Mashable How Oulu become a thriving startup ecosystem in 3 years - Arctic Startup Planning for progress: 18 Tips for a successful social media strategy - Search Engine Journal The secret to staying focused on work during the summer - DaveKerpen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>